DUOHAN ZHANG

 $\begin{aligned} &\text{Tel:}(+1)6089773453\\ &\text{dzhang}357@\text{wisc.edu} \end{aligned}$

Department of Statistics, University of Wisconsin Madison

SHORT BIO

Duohan Zhang is currently a master student of data science and statistics in Department of Statistics, University of Wisconsin Madison. He is very fortunate to work on an off-policy reinforcement learning(RL) project with Professor Josiah Hanna. Prior to that, he was a bachelor student in University of Science and Technology of China, majoring in statistics.

EDUCATION

University of Wisconsin Madison

Department of Statistics, master in Data Science

GPA: 3.82/4.0

University of Science and Technology of China

Department of Statistics, bachelor in statistics

Hefei, China 2018/9 - 2022/6

2021/9 - 2023/5

Madison, Wisconsin

Courses related to my research interests:

Statistical Learning: (100/100); Theory of Probability I: (94/100), a PhD level course; Theory of Probability II: a PhD level course, ranked 1st; Introduction to Statistical Learning Inference: (93/100); Real Analysis: (100/100); Functional Analysis: (93/100).

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Robust On-Policy Sampling for Data-efficient Policy Evaluation

2021/12 - 2022/5

University of Wisconsin Madison Advisor: Prof. Josiah Hanna

• Submitted paper "Robust On-Policy Sampling for Data-Efficient Policy Evaluation" to NeurIPS under review.

Online forgetting process for moderate linear regression

2021/2 - 2021/8

The university of science and technology of China

Advisor: Prof. Xiao Guo

- Motivated by the EU's "Right To Be Forgotten" regulation, we proposed a moderate dimensional regression in which past data has to be deleted while features are increasing at the same time.
- Proposed a new algorithm solving the problem.
- Unfortunately, we didn't continue to complete this project after I come to United States.

PUBLICATION

Robust On-Policy Sampling for Data-efficient Policy Evaluation. [Openreview]

Rujie Zhong, **Duohan Zhang**, Lukas Schäfer, Stefano V Albrecht, Josiah P. Hanna.

NeurIPS-2022 Poster

AWARDS

Student scholarship from USTC

2019,2020

School of Management, University of Science and Technology of China

SKILLS

Programming Languages and Tools

Python, Open AI gym, C++, R, LaTeX.

Language

TOEFL: 100(R 26, L 23, S 23, W 28).

GRE: $323+4.0(V\ 153,\ Q\ 170)$.